Speaker 1: - Carrie Lake is joining us tonight, and it's good to see you. I know you were very close to Charlie Kirk. I just wanna get your thoughts tonight. Go
Speaker 2: ahead. - Well, I mean, I'm devastated. I've been, my phone's been blowing up all afternoon, and I just haven't even had the words to talk to people. I called my daughter who worked for Charlie for a number of months, and then she went on to work for Turning Point Action, which was the political action part of Turning Point,
Speaker 3: and she was in tears. She's 22 years
old.
And
Speaker 3: Charlie meant that much to her. And, you know, she ended up leaving Turning Point. And I remember one of my last conversations, he was telling me how upset
Speaker 2: he was that Ruby was leaving. And I said, Charlie, Ruby followed your advice. You told kids that college is overrated. She didn't go to college. She instead got politically involved, worked for Turning Point. And
Speaker 4: now she's ready to settle down and start a family like you and Erica have. And he stopped and paused and he looked and he said...
Speaker 4: Well, that's a pretty good reason to leave and to get started on the next phase of her life. So I've just had a lot of great memories with Charlie. Of course, we're both Arizona residents. He lives in Arizona. He's made that his home. He's raising his family there. And I just can't believe he's gone. It hasn't sunk in yet. I'm saddened for Erica. I know she's incredibly strong in her faith. She comes from a very incredible family where she's a follower of Christ. And I think Erica is going
to have
Speaker 4: to lean on a strength that she didn't even know she had in the years to come to raise those two little ones and thinking they won't ever be able to be embraced by their father again but also knowing that she she understands the power of what charlie has created a 31 year old not just a movement not just a 501 c3 charlie realized it had to be more than that he created a huge impression in the media market, he created
a
Speaker 4: podcast then turned it into a popular radio show he wasn't just reaching young people i think the the misunderstanding people have about charlie kirk is he was just reaching the young vote he was reaching the young votes parents and grandparents and he had the biggest donor base of anybody i'd ever seen it wasn't just maga
Speaker 4: It
Speaker 3: was people who had never donated to politics before. It was people who were part of the establishment, but were curious and appreciated Charlie's approach to reaching the
Speaker 4: youth. And frankly, I truly believe Charlie was going to run for president, and he was going to be the youngest president we ever had, and possibly even in the next election. And that's a big threat to a lot of people, because Charlie had the donor base.
Speaker 4: Charlie had the movement, he had the apparatus, he had the volunteers, and he had the heart for it. And I know that we're still a long ways away from that election, but Charlie was a huge threat to a lot of people and not just, you know, the people that you can imagine he was. And he's only been on the planet for 31
Speaker 5: years, and he's been taken away from us, and I'm deeply saddened by that.
Speaker 6: Carrie, you know, one of the things, too, you talk about this massive donor base, and, you know, people don't understand how valuable.
Speaker 6: valuable
Speaker 7 (lower-pitched voice): that is in politics, but he was one of the few people that was actually, people donate to politics for whatever reason, people seek donations for political reasons for whatever reason. He was one of the first people who was like, this is what you're buying. You give me this much money, I will turn this many youth's mind into conservatives. He
Speaker 8: was the only person who ever quantified a political donation into a material item.
That's
Speaker 9: right. And he did it exactly that way. This amount of money can help us reach this many kids on every college campus. He did the same
Speaker 2: thing when it came to fraudulent elections. People have had it up to here with the way the elections are run. And I remember being at an event at Mar-a-Lago where they raised tens of millions of dollars saying, we know we can't turn elections around single handedly, but you know what we can do? We can
Speaker 4: go out and chase every single male in ballot.
Speaker 4: Whether you love him or hate him, and I hope you hate him because they're terrible. He said, we are going to go out and we're not going to let one mail-in ballot sit on one kitchen counter. We will chase every
Speaker 2: one of them. And Turning Point and Charlie Kirk are part of the reason, a big part of the reason President Trump is sitting in the Oval Office right now. They motivated an army of not just young people. I know because I'm in Arizona and we worked to chase the ballot. And I remember 60 and
Speaker 2: 70-year-old people who were going door to door, knocking on doors in Arizona, making sure that people filled out those ballots
Speaker 4: and got them turned in. And that's a very powerful, powerful thing. He spread it beyond, it started with, we have to reach the young people, and it moved beyond that. But the most important thing I think Charlie
Speaker 2: did, and I know if he were here, he would agree, he started something called Turning Point Faith.
I
Speaker 2: don't know if it was, you know, a overly cool thing to do, maybe for young people, maybe they didn't think it was, but Charlie felt
Speaker 4: it was important. And Charlie, he handed over his life to Jesus Christ. And Charlie meant that it wasn't just words. It wasn't just a tweet.
Speaker 4: Every single week he appeared at
Speaker 3: another church a mega church People showed up people who had maybe maybe kind of gotten away from their faith and they handed their lives back
Speaker 4: to Christ and I think that was the most powerful thing Charlie did and The thing that is giving me solace today is knowing that when I saw that video and I realized after after looking at the video Survival
for
Speaker 2: Charlie was going to be very difficult. I immediately knew that
But
Speaker 2: I know he's going to be with Christ. I know he's going to be with our Savior.
And I know
Speaker 2: that Erica feels that way as well. As difficult as the
Speaker 4: road ahead is for her, they have deep faith. And I think about the thousands of people that he helped bring back to salvation. And that's what really matters. And we heard our president say that about a week or two ago. He said, I'm trying to bring peace. I want to save lives. I'm trying to make it to heaven. And that's what it's really about.
And I
Speaker 4: truly believe that Charlie right
Speaker 10: now...
in
Speaker 10: heaven.
Speaker 11: Kari very briefly you mentioned the
Speaker 12 (lower-pitched voice): enemies you know that we what we know the predictable enemies on the left out but you seem to be referring to other enemies we don't know or unaware of or unlikely enemies do you remember saying that and what what did you mean by that?
Speaker 2: Well I just think there's I'm here in DC I'm away from my family I'm here in DC there's a lot of power veins of power
Speaker 4: And, you know, people aren't I'm in the here and now I'm saying, how can we work right now in this administration to be effective
Speaker 3: in bringing about President Trump's administration? There's a lot of people in this town who are looking two and four and six and eight years down the road and they're they're trying to bide their time and say, if we can slow Trump down.
Speaker 3: we'll go on to the next election and the next election and i think charlie had a political
Speaker 4: future that was bigger than maybe anybody expected and not only did he have the aspiration for that
Speaker 13: possibly but he had the apparatus to effectuate that and that is a dangerous man to a lot of people no
Speaker 14: just the youth vote he would have had them throughout the
Speaker 15: rest of his life and his career absolutely carrie lake so sorry for your loss and thank you so much for being with us tonight It's a loss to our whole country. It is. Well said.